We won't get another chance like this!
So let's enjoy it!
Nervous?
Pft! In your dreams!
Finally, the Outside Kids...
I-I mean, I'll do my best!
I'm walking on asphalt.
What of it?!
Okay.
Let's go, MayoPan!
Starring in TSUMA FES Extreme!
Making final batten height adjustments!
The road to one million subscribers...
Step three: collabing with famous streamers!
TSUMA-shi-san, how's it look?
Extremely good!
TSUMA-shi
Legendary streamer
known as the Stream God
TSUMA-shi!
The legendary streamer known as the Stream God!
And we even get to collab
with my hero, TSUMA-shi-san!
MayoPan
Okay, all eyes on me!
Here's the rundown!
Mayonaka Punch
The event is split up into two parts!
Part one is the collab segments!
Part two is our original performance!
We'll get everyone's attention during
the collab performances in part one,
and then unveil a song as MayoPan for
our original performance in part two!
Followed by a music video going up
on our channel right after the event!
A perfect plan to double our subscribers!
All TSUMA FES participants,
please gather in the main green room!
Okay, let's go!
Main Green Room
We're MayoPan!
Thanks for having us today!
Thank you!
Isn't that Masakichi?
Oh, the former Hype-Sis member?
Hype-Sis
MayoPan!
Glad to have you here!
Thanks for coming!
U-Um, th-thank you kindly for
giving us this opportunity today—
There's nothing I love more
than seeing fresh talent grow!
Let's get along and have fun
making today's event a success!
So precious...
Ah, shoot.
Gotta introduce ourselves.
Y-You two are...
Taromaru and Salamin!
We'll be your emcees for tonight!
F. Taromaru
[Muscle Channel
with F. Taromaru]
Muscle-building streamer
popular with thirty-somethings
for his "No-Sweat Workouts."
F. Taromaru!
A muscle-building streamer popular with
thirty-somethings for his "No-Sweat Workouts"!
[Salami N. Cappuccino's Prattle Palace]
Chats about the mundane with a unique sense for words.
Beauty streamer popular with women in her age group.
Salami N. Cappuccino
Salami N. Cappuccino!
A beauty streamer popular with
women in the same age group!
Salamin!
I watch you so much,
my phone screen might crack!
That stare of yours is like a destroyer!
Let's see. First up, for the music collab...
That'd be me!
Oh, Fu-san!
You're raring to go!
Th-This collab is a dream come true for me!
Mm-hmm.
Well, about your collab partners...
Dang...
What?!
Outlaw and Sidebrah from the Outside Kids
are a no-show for the music collab?!
So sorry!
N-No way...
Huh?
Then what about the parts
sung by the Outside Kids?
If they're not here,
we'll have to split them between us.
Shura
Female singer renowned for the contrast
between her beautiful singing and
intense screams. Her most-watched
video boasts over 40 million views!
Shura!
The female singer renowned for the contrast
between her beautiful singing
and intense screams!
It's just us two. Bring it on.
Nice to meet you—
Whoo!
The game collab is with these whoopers!
Nice to meet you, Tokage-san!
Juwa-chan
[Juwa Channel]
Solo entertainer popular for ultra-wacky
slapstick variety segments. Ugly-cute
Juwa-chan merch is hot amongst
grade schoolers.
Juwa-chan!
A solo entertainer popular for his
ultra-wacky slapstick variety segments!
Electric Eel Energy!
Electric Eel Energy
Variety channel by a two-man unit. High-frequency,
high-quality videos guaranteed to split your sides.
The members are Daifuku Minister and Garden Eel.
A high-frequency, high-quality variety channel,
run by the duo of
Daifuku Minister and Garden Eel!
I try so hard to avoid people like them.
Daifuku
Care for some daifuku?
Whoo!
Busting out the daifuku already?!
Tokage-san, let's have fun today!
Whoo!
Whoo...
And for the cooking collab...
Hey, there. I'm Cast Iron Ken.
[Cast Iron Ken Channel]
Culinary specialist
who lives by the motto,
"Everyday cooking should be
tasty, fun, and easy!"
Cast Iron Ken
Cast Iron Ken!
A culinary specialist who lives by the motto,
"Everyday cooking
should be tasty, fun, and easy!"
I'm Ichiko from MayoPan!
Um, your stuffed bell peppers
really blew my mind!
They don't fall apart, right?
You're amazing too, Ichiko-chan,
always making such huge portions.
How long have you been cooking?
About a hundred years!
A hundred years?
Huh?
Live, where's your quiz collab
partner, Plumb Wrong Logic?
Let's see, Pochi-san's comment...
"The venue hall for today
looks quite run-down."
"Plumb Wrong Logic-san,
are you worried about a leaky roof?"
Well, it's true that run-down pipes
present a leaking risk,
but since it's not raining—
Plumb Wrong Logic
Construction streamer
who debates current affairs
while performing plumbing work
Plumb Wrong Logic!
A construction streamer who debates current
affairs while performing plumbing work!
You see, not a lot of people know this, but...
Plumb Wrong Logic-san, nice to meet—
Oh, Live-san, my collab partner.
Nice to meet you.
PVC pipes are made of
polyvinyl chloride, are they not?
Everyone!
We've got bottles of Mastamin Z
from our sponsor, AZO Pharma!
Let's get pumped with heels for this show!
Vampires pretending to be
humans for an event...
I swear, they're such a handful!
What, seriously?!
Hey, look at this!
This online news article is wild!
Wait, that's Plumb Wrong Logic!
Outlaw... Sidebrah...
Three! Two! One!
Yes, I do.
Yes, I do!
How do you do?
How do you do!
Hey, everyone! TSUMA-shi here!
Welcome to my TSUMA FES!
Without further ado, let's have
our participants take the stage!
First, introducing our two emcees!
F. Taromaru and Salami N. Cappuccino!
Sponsored by AZO Pharma's Mastamin Z!
Open it to be hit with the bubble fizz
of its strong carbonation!
Strong carbonation!
Next, the singer you all know and love, Shura!
It's starting!
I'm so nervous!
But now that it's underway,
we just have to get through it!
Let's keep 'em coming!
Ken, the culinary expert!
The construction streamer, Plumb Wrong Logic!
It's up to you now! Live! Ichiko! Fu! Tokage!
And now, the new, up-and-coming channel!
Mayonaka Punch!
Good morning from the dead of night!
Let's have a blast today!
I feel like a parent
watching their kid's school play!
Now that we've wrapped up the intros...
TSUMA FES Extreme!
Bomber!
TSUMA FES Extreme is finally underway!
From here on out,
your emcees will be me, Taromaru...
And me, Salamin!
Our first segment is... the music collab!
Sing along with mi sol la si do!
But unfortunately, well...
The Outside Kids are a no-show.
I did the same thing
for a part-time job once.
But this and that are different stories.
Music Collab!!
~Let's Sing Those Timeless Hits~
Now then, here are Fu
and Shura in their first collab.
Take it away.
S-Such intensity!
Ah, I need to sing...
Was the audience this big before?
Huh?
Huh? Where in the song are...
Okay!
For our next collab...
Game Collab!!
~This Ball & Chain is Nothing!
Red Light, Green Light~
A super-heavyweight game
of Red Light, Green Light!
No life comes without shackles!
Ichiko, you're up soon, so go wait off stage!
Roger!
The winner will be the first person
who touches TSUMA-shi!
So heavy...
All for me, one for me!
Okay, here we go!
Green light!
None of the contestants are budging!
A 30-kg weight is no joke!
Tokage-san!
Red light!
Green light...
Are you okay?
Those whooping frat boys are a bit much.
Hold it right there!
C-C-C-Could those voices be...
The Outside Kids, Outlaw and Sidebrah!
What?!
A last-minute entry
after ditching the music collab!
Green light, red light!
Stop!
Huh? Do we have more people?
Sure, why not?
Green light...
The game goes on!
And they don't have chains!
Red, red, red...
The two of us have always...
...gone outside what's common sense!
Oh, snap!
Light!
I'm first!
M-My word!
With speed that defies common sense,
MayoPan's Tokage is first!
Number one!
Why did you use your powers?!
Defying common sense?!
That's one hell of an understatement!
Tokage!
Love...
Dearie me.
The Outside Kids have suddenly made
confessions of love to Tokage!
So loud!
She'll pay.
Huh?
Okay, let's move on to the next segment.
Judge
I want to eat something yummy!
Cooking Collab:
Cooking Collab!!
~How Will This Combination Taste?~
How Will This Combination Taste?
Each chef will pick one card with a dish.
Combine the two culinary creations to
complete an outrageously good meal.
This one!
Mapo Tofu
This is...
Okay!
Let's get cooking!
Now, then, Ken's already
starting to prep his ingredients.
How about Ichiko?
She's deep in thought
while staring at the ingredients.
Whoa! Where's Ichiko off to?!
Is MayoPan's Ichiko running
for her life off the stage?!
What is she doing?!
Ichiko!
Where did you go?!
For the love of...
I'm back!
I was missing some ingredients,
so I went to buy them!
Hurry up and get back out there!
Cast Iron Ken's working that wok like a pro!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Oh, Ichiko has returned!
Where have you been, Ichiko?
Sheesh.
I would have gone instead if she'd asked.
I'm back.
There you are, alien tacos!
Amigo!
Live?
I'll take care of you lot!
Huh?
A tortilla punch?!
Not-cho fast!
Don't tell me...
[Ingredients]
Mastamin
Mastamin concentrate
Honey
Garlic
Garlic extract
Citric acid
Vitamin B2
Royal jelly
Guarana extract
Caffeine
Okay!
Both chefs have completed their dish!
First up, Cast Iron Ken!
It's fried rice!
Now that looks good!
Let's see what Ichiko's whipped up!
It might not have set yet, but...
A perfect complement, mapo tofu—
A-Almond tofu?!
Almond tofu?!
Milk
There wasn't any milk!
Sorry, but your dish was mapo tofu!
What?!
I bombed the song,
and Tokage-san stole my faves.
I've been instilled with fear and trauma.
I misread the kanji and made the wrong dish.
You're fine! The crowd loved it!
Mapo... Mapo...
Live-san from MayoPan!
It's time for your performance,
so please come right away!
No choice now.
Live, let's go!
Time for the quiz collab!
Yukichi Survivor
Reia
Plumb Wrong Logic
Live
Quiz Collab!!
~Lightning Fast! 100-Question Quiz in 10 Minutes~
A hundred questions in ten minutes
to make the emcees cry!
Six seconds per question? No way!
Plumb Wrong Logic-san,
how are you feeling about this quiz?
Plumb Wrong Logic-san?
Oh, looks like he's clammed up from nerves.
Put away those wings.
Why don't we just say he's all fired up?
Don't fly. Promise me you won't fly.
Okay, it's just about time we get started...
All right, then go on!
Oh, here's Live-san from MayoPan!
Hi-yah!
That moron!
She's flying?!
M-MayoPan's Live, with an explosive entrance!
Time to start our lightning-fast quiz!
Don't fly, don't fly, don't fly!
Don't you fly again!
If you get kicked out, there goes
our last chance to make a comeback!
What do I do?!
Okay, question number one!
Known as the "abalone of the fields,"
what's TSUMA-shi's favorite vegetable?
Go ahead, Plumb Wrong Logic-san.
I sincerely apologize for my actions!
Too bad.
TSUMA-shi's favorite vegetable is
zha cai, not an apology!
Taro-chan, look.
Hm?
Top > NewTuber Roundup > NewTuber Scandals
Affair Uncovered!!
Plumb Wrong Logic, NewTuber With Over
1.6 Million Subscribers, Found Cheating
An apology was the right answer!
I truly have nothing to say for myself!
Get out!
Don't ruin this event!
What a mess.
Live, just get through this somehow!
Not good!
She's gonna float up!
The Plumb-san news is real, huh?
What does this mean for the quiz collab?
That's it!
Let me borrow that!
What? H-Hey!
Here.
What's that?
Hang this rope down from the ceiling!
Hang down? Ceiling?
Don't talk back! Just do it!
Okay, Ichiko, let's go.
Okay.
Fu, you'll turn into a bat and get behind Live,
hook the rope onto her,
and then hold her down so she doesn't fly up.
What?!
Pull her down from below
so she doesn't fly away,
and even if she does,
we can explain it away with the rope!
Th-That's absurd!
Okay, bat time!
What?
I'm really, truly sorry for what I've done!
Now!
All right!
Now we should be fine either way!
Ten minutes have passed!
Time's up!
We'll have to save the other ninety-nine
questions for some other day!
No way!
Our comeback chance!
Milk does get rid of garlic odor, but...
we're talking almond tofu fried rice here!
Anything's worth a shot at this point.
The almond tofu and fried rice
are happily having an affair.
That's the dream I had.
Yes?
Sorry to intrude.
TSUMA-shi-san?!
Um, I'm sorry for how Live acted earlier...
No, I should be the one apologizing!
So sorry about Plumb Wrong Logic!
He ruined Live's first time on stage!
TSUMA-shi-san! Don't—
Non!
I'll get the crowd fired up for part two!
Let's make it an extremely great time together!
Yes!
See you!
Masaki?
TSUMA-shi-san's doing so much for us,
but we haven't managed to do anything!
We can't go back like this!
Not on my watch!
We'll make sure our song
as MayoPan is a success!
Let's make it a stellar performance!
Go, MayoPan!
Yeah!
Huh, what?
A blackout?
Sorry, everyone!
Looks like we lost power!
We're looking into what caused it,
so be patient for a little longer!
Okay!
Why'd the power go out?
My house lost power once from a water leak.
The pipes rusted away.
We might be able to fix the blackout.
What?
I'll go take care of it!
But how?
Be careful in the dark
or you could hurt yourself!
Don't you want to redeem your reputation?
That's asking for a lot!
It's fine, it's fine!
The least we can do is try!
A short circuit?
That's right!
There might be a leak in this run-down venue!
I'm gonna make the crowd
hear their song, no matter what!
Look! There!
That's not related to the power outage.
Why not?
There's no circuitry near that leak.
That's plumb wrong logic.
Screw you!
What now, then?!
Yukirinko knows who did it!
Huh?
Mastamin Z!
It's no use.
Let's call it off.
What?!
We can't keep the audience
waiting any longer.
TSUMA-shi-san!
Hey! There's no one here!
Whazzis?
Found a cute ribbon!
Under there?
Ribbon-san, are you trying
to rack up views, too?
Are Outlaw and Sidebrah coming?
We'll sing!
You can't be serious!
There's no audio or lighting!
It's fine!
Our Masaki will figure it out!
Besides, even without a mic, I'm pretty loud.
We'll go ahead without mics!
And if it doesn't work out, we'll beg on our
knees, or stomachs, or whatever you want.
How 'bout it? Will you gamble on us?
You said it, Tokage-nee-san!
Okay.
Let's give it a shot, then!
TSUMA FES Extreme...
Bomber!
Ow!
That hurts, damn it!
Yes, this will mean it never happened.
Even if it was scripted,
that confession is just too awful.
Hey, wait! That cable!
I'll be the one to protect those two!
Hand it over already!
Thank you all so, so much for your patience!
I know it's still dark,
but we're starting the second half!
First up on stage will be...
Mayonaka Punch!
Let go already!
I won't let anyone get in the way of our love!
Keep it up! Keep it up!
Stop tripping and help me, you old fart!
I'll be the one to save the two of them!
We've worked so hard preparing for today!
We need people like you
to hit the subscribe button,
so we've spent countless hours
coming up with ideas!
I swear...
I was the one who wanted to see it the most.
Huh?
Today's event got us even closer
to one million subs!
Now I can finally upsize my beef bowls!
That's right! You can even add an egg!
An egg?!
With tonjiru on the side!
Tonjiru!
Next time: "Welcome.
This Is Your New Family Home Now!"
Welcome. This Is Your New Family Home Now!
Order up! One large, add an egg and tonjiru!
The big dream I've waited for!